Daniel Tiburcio Buarao

I hold a Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, with a Specializing in technical support for both hardware and software systems. In addition to my academic qualifications, I am deeply committed to web development and have acquired substantial experience in social media marketing and sales.

Daniel-Buarao in

+639-295-686-871

WORK EXPERIENCE

Online Business I Self-Employed Puff deck

01/2023 - 05/2023

- Managing Business Page.
- Creating ads Design for promoting the Product
- **Negotiate Contracts and Monitored** Costumer Service quality.
- Researched market trends and identified opportunities for product development or expansion.

Technical Support Engineer (On-the-job Training) Tech Mahindra

08/2023 - 11/2023

- Solving Computer tech issue for the Staff members.
- Setting up hardware and software.
- Managing and maintaining the computer
- Configuring TCP/IP Addressing using APIPA method.
- Perform troubleshooting of Lan and Connectivity issues.
- Perform Move station and setup.
- Install, Support and diagnose Basic Application software for the Company such as Citrix, RTclient etc.

Property Consultant

DMCI Homes

04/2024 - 09/2024

- Managing Business Page.
- Creating ads Design for promoting the Product
- Negotiate Contracts and Monitored Costumer Service quality. Digital Marketing

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web Development:

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT.

Computer Management Skills:

Hardware Development, Analysis, and Testing Network Configuration, Technical Support and Troubleshooting.

Sales Skills:

Product Expertise, Negotiating, Social Media Selling.

SOFT SKILLS

Written and oral communication

Attention to detail Public speaking Peer collaboration

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

ICCT COLLEGES

2019 - 2023

Accountancy Business and Management

Tañong High School

2013 - 2019

CERTIFICATES AND LICENSES

CCNAv7: Introduction to Networks

Cisco Networking Academy

Udemy: Website Creation

Website Creation: Start learning from the beginning.

Udemy: HTML

The Complete Guide to HTML for Beginners

Udemy: JavaScript for Beginners

The A-to-Z course to Mastering JavaScript

Udemy: HTML5 & CSS3 Complete Course

Build Website like a Pro

Udemy: JavaScript for Beginners Complete Course

Learn JavaScript Programming Language with Practical Interaction.

Udemy: Next.Js Web Dev: React Framework

Next.Js Mastery: Harnessing React, Advanced Routing, Seamless API Integration, and web optimization Strategies